Tegar **IBRAHIM**

Management Business of Telecommunication and Information

Griya Caraka Resident, H-21 Bandung, West Java, 40293, Indonesia

i Born, November 19th 1990 at Cirebon (Indonesia), Citizenship, Indonesian



Self-starter with strong communication and leadership skills. proven academic and curricular achievements, possess soft skills required to propel the organization achieving its objectives. Telkom University graduate with Business Information, Management Information System, Security Audit, Information Security System background and years of experiences as a Cyber Security Analyst, Penetration Tester and digital forensics as well as managing information technology within The Ministry of Health of The Republic of Indonesia Government Bureaucratic Information and Technology Work Unit.

COMPETENCES

Scripting Python, rubyonrail, PHP, Javascript, HTML, CSS, bash

Data Base Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL, phpMyAdmin

Development Tools Visual Studio Code, git

Operating systems Mac OS X, Windows Server, Windows 11, Kali Linux, Parrot Linux, Ubuntu

> Other Data Management, Digital Business Marketing, E-Commerce Strategy Analyst and Planning,

Information Security Audit



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Latest

Pusat Pelatihan SDMK Kementerian Kesehatan | IT Staff, Training Accreditation, General Bureau

2020 - 2022

- > Assessing Web Application Development process
- > Penetration and Stress Testing
- > Making Adjustment and Updating Web Application
- > Making Report Document

Ministry Of Health

June 2019

Sekretariat Konsil Tenaga Kesehatan Indonesia | IT Staff, REGISTRATION, E - STR ver 2.0

2019 - 2020

- > Supporting Helpdesk Team related upon system troubleshooting
- > Updating and Maintaining Web Application
- > Implementing E-sign (generating p12 and collaborating and connecting API from BSrE (Balai Sertifikasi Elektronik) from BSSN (Badan Siber dan Sandi Negara) for E-certificate (E-STR)
- > Penetration and Stress Testing
- > Making Report Document

Ministry Of Health | BSrE | BSSN

February 2017

PT. Dee Sukses Indonesia | General Manager, CINEMA INFORMATION SYSTEM DEVELOPMENT, Jakarta -**Bogor**

2017-2019

- > Creating SOP and System workflow for Cinema Development
- > Creating and Maintaining Information System for ticketing within the business process
- > Assessing Market with SWOT approach
- > Set Up and Maintaining advance cinema Projector System (BARCO)
- > Preparing Movie from DRC to Projector System Software

June 2015

PT. Ikhwan Mega Power, PROJECT PLANNER, Project Reporter | West Sumatera Indonesia

2015-2016

- Hydroelectric Power Plant pour Construction Development Project
 - > Making WorkPlan Schedule
 - > Checking and Reporting Work Progress
 - > Surveying area within Job Site

April 2012

Bizzpack, PRODUCT DESIGNER, Market Analyst

2012-2013

- a startup company engaged in backpack manufacturing and sales
 - > Creating and Designing Backpack and any visual design related
 - > Creating and Designing e-commerce website

Bizzpack





English



- > Passion
- > Positive Motivation
- > Initiative

FORMATION

2009-2013

Faculty of Telkom Economy and Business School, Management Business of Telecommunication and Information - Telkom University Major Subjects: Business Management, Marketing Management, Economics Data Management, Organization Behavior, Operation and Quality Management, Management Information System, Business Information, Business Strategy, Information Security Audit, Information Security System, Strategy Management.

Final Year Project (Degree) - Consumer Preferences Analysis Toward Smartphones in Bandung within the year 2013. The objective is to find out and design how the preferences of consumers in Bandung and what was the ideal product profile or preferred smartphone.

I graduate from Telkom University within Management Business of Telecommunication and Information. Bachelor of Business Management in September 2013 with 3.23/4 GPA. Area of specialization: Business Management, Information Security Audit and Development.

2006-2009 Darul Hikam Senior Highschool

2003-2006 Yayasan Pendidikan Jayawijaya Junior Highschool

PROJECTS

 $\mathsf{OSCP}_x kyrage$

 \Box https://github.com/xkyrage/OSCP $_xkyrage$ \Box Offensive Security Certified Professional Repository CreatingRepository for ConductingPentest.

BASH PHP JAVASCRIPT PYTHON VISUAL STUDIO CODE

HAMMERDDOS PROJECT 2013 - 2014

f O github.com/https://github.com/xkyrage/HAMMER $_d dos$ f C Script Githubpage Creating Script tools for Hammering and simple distributed denial-of-service DDOS.

python



Muhammad Kharisma Putra Tamara

AVP of Retention (Digital Touchpoint), INDOSAT OOREDOO

@ derry.kharisma@yahoo.com

+6285920694940